{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227105214","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227105214"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_a_z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227112702","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227112702"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_a_z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227122987","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227122987"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_a_z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227129632","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227129631"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_b_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227137227","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227137227"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_b_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227147548","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227147547"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_b_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227153791","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227153791"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_b_j"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227160451","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227160450"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_o_b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227168035","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227168035"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_o_b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227178334","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227178334"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_o_b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227184536","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227184536"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_b_i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227191176","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227191174"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_h_b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227197814","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227197814"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_e_r"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227205331","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227205331"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_e_r"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227215613","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227215612"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_e_r"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227221847","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227221847"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_r_m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227229374","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227229374"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_r_m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227239680","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227239679"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_r_m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227245899","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227245899"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_g_b"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227252593","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227252593"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_f_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227260097","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227260097"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_f_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227270386","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227270386"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_f_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227279362","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227279362"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_b_f_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227288633","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227288632"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e484c8bc-2517-4146-a109-c1c7eca8ccef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_b_f_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227299269","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227299269"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227300317","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227300316"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227303217","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227303216"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227304260","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227304260"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227313311","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227313311"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227314372","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227314372"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227317127","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227317127"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227318165","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227318165"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227321037","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227321036"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227322077","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227322077"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227325650","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227325650"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227326691","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227326691"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227333358","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227333358"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227334150","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227334150"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227334248","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227334248"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" 4178dcf0-8cc7-4e7b-8400-31c85c14aae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227344502","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227344502"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e020be35-4e31-4f7c-87e6-21fafbad2695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_73"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227345146","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227345146"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e020be35-4e31-4f7c-87e6-21fafbad2695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_73"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227345361","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227345361"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e020be35-4e31-4f7c-87e6-21fafbad2695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_73"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227345616","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227345615"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e020be35-4e31-4f7c-87e6-21fafbad2695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_73"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227345707","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227345706"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" e020be35-4e31-4f7c-87e6-21fafbad2695"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_73"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227354276","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227354275"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" abb672bc-1ad6-4de7-a053-9497dcf461c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227356366","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227356365"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" abb672bc-1ad6-4de7-a053-9497dcf461c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227358260","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227358259"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" abb672bc-1ad6-4de7-a053-9497dcf461c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227358317","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227358317"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" abb672bc-1ad6-4de7-a053-9497dcf461c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227364536","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227364535"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" abb672bc-1ad6-4de7-a053-9497dcf461c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227372599","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227372599"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" abb672bc-1ad6-4de7-a053-9497dcf461c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_75","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227383452","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227383451"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" abb672bc-1ad6-4de7-a053-9497dcf461c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227392973","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227392972"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227393351","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227393350"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227393846","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227393846"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227394191","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227394191"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227394603","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227394602"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227395085","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227395085"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227395314","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227395314"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227398542","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227398542"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227398585","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227398585"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227399313","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227399313"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227399711","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227399711"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227400009","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227400009"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227400222","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227400221"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227400423","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227400423"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227400747","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227400747"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227400980","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227400980"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227404147","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227404147"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227404556","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227404555"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227407112","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227407112"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227407315","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227407315"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227407523","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227407523"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227410996","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227410996"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227414753","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227414753"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227415784","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227415783"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227418483","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227418483"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227418857","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227418857"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227419340","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227419340"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227419688","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227419688"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227420098","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227420098"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227420581","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227420580"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227420811","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227420811"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227423990","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227423989"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227424027","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227424027"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227424741","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227424740"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227425141","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227425141"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227425442","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227425442"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227425652","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227425652"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227425863","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227425863"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227426185","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227426184"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227426414","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227426414"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227429013","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227429012"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227429087","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227429087"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d7609b6c-488a-4c76-b430-c864e7bd0e01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227439164","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227439164"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227447225","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227447224"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227453408","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227453407"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227457587","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227457586"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227463812","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227463812"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227468275","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227468274"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227474848","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227474847"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227481515","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227481515"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227485921","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227485921"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227489901","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227489901"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227493781","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227493781"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227500000","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227500000"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227504578","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227504578"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227511454","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227511454"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227515472","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227515472"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550227528856","data":{"timestamp":" 1550227528856"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_133754"," gameId":" d6904f78-618f-4122-9ef2-ab8cd22fa827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}